BARBARA: Previously on Gotham...
Oh, no. Help me! Help
me! Somebody help!
COBBLEPOT: They think she
might have fallen asleep at the wheel.
ED: Her brake lines were cut.
Which leaves one
conclusion. Murder.
And I know who did it.
Hold on, Butch.
IVY: I might be in
trouble. I stole a necklace.
BRUCE: Why is this
necklace so important?
What makes someone kill for it?
- What is it?
- A key.
SELINA: We need to go somewhere.
BRUCE: We'll go to my house.
You two are a couple now?
- No.
- Yes.
My engagement announcement is
coming out in the Gazette tomorrow.
And it will feature Mario's
name. His family name.
JIM: You mean Falcone?
Such a beautiful space
for a rehearsal dinner.
We can't thank you enough.
And did Roberto's food
live up to all my hype?
Are you kidding?
(SIGHS) Any more burrata,
and I wouldn't fit into my
wedding dress. (CHUCKLES)
I can't believe we're
getting married in two days.
Have you two settled on
a honeymoon destination?
Uh, no, but Lee finally agreed
to take some time off of work.
With everything going on, I didn't
wanna leave anybody in the lurch.
I was very sorry to hear
about Captain Barnes.
He's a good man. What he
did was due entirely to the virus.
What's truly frightening is that
nobody knew. Nobody could see it.
There aren't any symptoms?
Well, looking back now, there were signs.
Increased strength, emotional instability.
Nothing he couldn't hide.
DR. THOMPKINS: The lab
analyzing Alice Tetch's blood
has developed a test to
see if someone's infected.
- You're kidding. When?
- They just finished.
It's a step toward
finding a cure.
How are we? Good?
Wonderful, Roberto. We
can't wait for tomorrow night.
Oh! Your rehearsal
dinner's gonna be fantastico.
We're gonna take
care of everything.
It's a privilege to serve
you again, Don Falcone.
Don Falcone, please,
we'll pull your car around.
Yeah, okay.
- Wonderful evening, Roberto.
- You're welcome.
- I love you.
- (SOFT CHUCKLE) I love you, too.
(BOTH GRUNT)
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
(SIRENS WAILING)
MALE WAITER 1: You don't
understand anything, okay?
My friend just got blown up. Now,
I wanna know what happened?
Can you explain that to me?
We need to talk.
Is everyone okay?
A few first degree burns,
but that's it. They were lucky.
Any idea who might
have done this?
I've made my share of enemies
over the years. Could be anyone.
Why come after you now?
My oldest son is
getting married.
When better to settle an old
score and hurt me and my family?
Maybe.
Or maybe someone thinks
you're coming out of retirement?
- I'm not.
- Good.
Doesn't mean I'm gonna stand
by after something like this.
The Captain of Police was just
indicted for murder and sent to Arkham.
The last thing I need is you and your
men tearing up Gotham, looking for revenge.
I didn't start this.
I'll get to the bottom
of it. You have my word.
I'll give you one day.
COBBLEPOT: As members of
the five families, you are well aware
that with the tragic
downfall of Captain Barnes,
people are frightened.
They will be looking to
us for stability, to feel safe.
So,
how does a 50% increase
on protection fees sound?
- (LAUGHTER)
- BARBARA: Sounds a little steep to me.
What do we have here?
A little family reunion?
My invitation get
lost in the mail?
No, this meeting is for grown-ups,
so I'm gonna have to ask you to leave.
Hmm.
Quick question.
(GUNS COCKING)
Is it, "How do I commit suicide?"
Because that answer is coming.
Tabitha and Butch are
missing. Where are they?
I have no idea.
I have not seen Butch since his little
summer stock revival of the Red Hood Gang.
Let's cut the crap. Shall we?
Tabitha has been helping Butch
hide since your little victory celebration.
They're an item now, barf...
She's supposed to check in
every night, and she hasn't.
She's not answering her
phone, and no one has seen her.
And you think I took them?
Obviously.
(MUFFLED LAUGHTER)
How about this,
you lower your gun
and beg my forgiveness
for this gross insubordination,
and I might let you
walk out of here alive.
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
My apologies.
They must have run off
somewhere without telling me.
Love makes people do
crazy things, doesn't it?
We have a history, you and I.
But if you ever point
a gun at me again,
Olga will be cleaning
your brains off the floor.
She's a real wiz with stains.
Bye, Pengy.
Everyone out, now!
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
Are you checking up on me?
What? No.
Barbara Kean was just
here. She's looking for them.
- So?
- So, are you finished yet?
We've talked about this. I need
to work through my grief my way.
COBBLEPOT: Of
course, and I support you.
Any chance you could work
through it a smidge faster?
I am swamped today.
(DIAL TONE)
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
Sorry you had to hear that.
He can just be so self-centered.
- What were we talking about?
- I'm gonna kill you!
Oh! Right, how I
found you. (LAUGHING)
Well, it wasn't hard.
The next time you
wanna disappear,
consider taking a sabbatical
from your favorite restaurant.
Your love of Gusto's Eggplant
Parmesan isn't exactly a state secret.
- (MUFFLED GROANS)
- Come here.
That, with a healthy amount of
Midazolam in your food to knock you out.
A hundred bucks to your
delivery boy, who, by the way,
I get the feeling hasn't been
being tipped very well, Butch.
(MUFFLED SPEECH)
I'm sorry. What was that?
(MUFFLED) You're gonna regret
this! You're gonna regret this.
If you touch one hair on
her head, I swear I'll kill you.
Save your strength, big
guy. You're gonna need it.
And you tell Penguin
he's a coward.
If he wants me dead,
- he should come here and do it like a man.
- (DEVICE POWERING UP)
This has nothing
to do with Penguin.
And you are the coward.
Killing an innocent woman.
What? Who?
Isabella.
She was my everything,
and you took her from me!
What in the hell are
you talkin' about?
I was hoping you'd be difficult.
- (ELECTRICITY ZAPPING)
- (GROANING)
(LAUGHING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Hey. You okay?
Stomach.
Being acting captain is
such a strain, why do it?
I'm the senior guy around here.
- What about Tuttle?
- Tuttle?
Guy shot a cat last week.
- On purpose?
- Does it matter?
Look, I might not have always
seen eye-to-eye with Barnes,
but he was a good captain.
Least I can do is
keep his seat warm
until they find some
kind of cure for this virus.
Detective Gordon, car
bomb used a mercury switch
with military grade plastic.
That's kind of high
end for a mob hit.
That's not all.
The explosive was laced
with some sort of accelerant.
Made the explosion burn at 10
times the heat of standard C-4.
Whoever set this bomb
didn't want anything left behind.
Only one guy I know
with that level of expertise.
Ex-military nut job, goes
by the name of "Fuse."
(SIRENS WAILING)
This is our guy.
Not for nothing, ensuring Don Falcone's
safety is not why I wear the badge.
- It's not just about him.
- You mean Lee?
If you're worried, you could tell her not
to marry the son of a former crime boss.
GCPD!
Dead, but still warm.
Whoever did this
must've just left.
So, whoever hired Fuse to plant the
bomb doesn't want any loose ends?
Looks like he was
on his way out of town.
Must have figured his
employers weren't that forgiving.
- Guy can pack, I'll give him that much.
- Once a soldier, always a soldier.
Bed sheets aren't tucked in.
Times, locations,
surveillance photos.
- This doesn't make any sense.
- What?
Carmine's not the target.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(MOTORCYCLE REVVING)
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
(TIRES SCREECH)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
- Down!
- (GUNSHOTS)
What the hell's going on?
Carmine's not
the target. You are.
Et, euh, voilà.
Thank you very
much, Master Bruce.
What is this?
That is a Pennyworth
signature frittata.
It's a crustless quiche.
It's eggs, miss.
Just eat it, will you?
Where's your mate, anyway?
Conservatory.
Girl loves it there.
Well, she's hardly what
you call "a girl," is she?
Yeah. Well, thanks for
the crustless egg thing.
But I got errands to run.
Uh, no, sorry, miss. No
one is to leave the house
until we find exactly
who is following you.
It's been days. I
can't take it anymore.
I'm sorry. What is it
exactly that you object to?
Is it the gourmet food, or the king-size
double-bed with the Egyptian linen?
Would you tell the help here that I
can come and go as I please? Please?
Alfred's right. It's not safe
for you to be in Gotham alone.
(SCOFFS) I've been in
Gotham alone my whole life.
I can take care of
myself. Nothing's changed.
Yeah, you've made that clear.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Nothing.
Those men were willing to kill
for this key, we need to know why.
I'll be in the study.
There's more books I
haven't gone through.
There has to be a reference
to the key somewhere.
And have you stopped to consider
that maybe it's just an old key?
No.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACH)
I'll get you some
breakfast, miss.
You know, some of these plants
would do much better in direct sunlight.
Could you turn off the alarm,
so I can put them outside?
Well, maybe later. I'd rather not you be
walking around the grounds on your own.
Can you smell this?
Beg your pardon?
Right here.
(EXHALES DEEPLY) What is that?
Just a mix of clove,
fenugreek, and yarrow root oils.
It's lovely.
- It is, isn't it?
- Yeah.
Now, I need you to tell
me something, okay?
Anything.
How do you turn off the alarm?
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
This doesn't make any sense.
Do you know anyone
who might want you dead?
- You can't be serious.
- Everyone has enemies.
No, Detective. They don't.
Regardless, you need
to limit your exposure.
Lay low for a while until I
can find out who's behind this.
How do you propose I do that?
I'm picking up our
wedding rings this afternoon.
Lee and I are getting
married tomorrow.
Oh.
You want me to
cancel the wedding.
- I just wanna keep you safe.
- I'd bet you'd love that.
I run home to Lee.
Tell her we need to hide until
Detective Gordon can save the day?
- This is not a time for ego.
- Are you talking to me about ego?
How do I even know you're
gonna be able to find him?
- Or that you'll even try?
- You need to trust me.
Whoever is behind this is gonna
keep coming until they get the job done.
If that's true, it doesn't matter
where we go, or what we do.
As long as I got a target
on my back, Lee isn't safe.
- Hey.
- Yeah.
Keep an eye on Mario, don't let
him leave. What are you doing?
- I'm keeping an eye on Mario.
- Don't look at him.
What the hell's going on?
I don't know. Something doesn't
fit. I need to talk to Carmine.
Maybe once he knows Mario's the
target, something will jog his memory.
Just keep it...
I got it. I got it.
(DOOR LOCK OPENS)
Hello, Comrade.
Comrade is not Russian word.
- Oh, shut up. Of course, it is.
- You shouldn't be here.
Relax. I know Penguin's
out for a few hours.
I just wanna talk.
I don't know anything.
Listen. I grew up
in a place like this.
A large staff of people
always coming and going.
Listening. You can't
help but overhear things.
Is handsome ring.
(GASPS) It is.
And very expensive.
I bet it would look
just fabulous on you.
(CHUCKLING)
(CLEARS THROAT)
Mr. Penguin, he treat me
nice. I have warm feeling for him.
But the other one...
Nygma?
I don't know why
Mr. Penguin likes him so much.
He could do better.
Wait. You mean likes, likes?
Wow. Okay, we should
definitely revisit that another time.
But what about Nygma? Did he
say anything about my missing friend?
I don't know.
But I hear Mr. Nygma
talking about special delivery.
But nothing come
to the house, but bill.
"Stocks & Bondage?"
- (ELECTRICITY ZAPPING)
- (LAUGHING)
(GROANING)
(MUFFLED GRUNTS)
BUTCH: How many
times do I have to tell you?
I have never even
heard of this woman.
- (ELECTRICITY ZAPS)
- (GRUNTS)
Well, then I suppose I should
put my attention elsewhere.
BUTCH: No! No!
- Leave her out of this!
- ED: Afraid I can't do that.
She is an integral
part of your penance.
It was such a pleasant
surprise when I discovered
that the two of you were
together. (LAUGHING)
You know, after
the initial gag reflex.
You know, I bet this
girl doesn't even exist.
I mean, come on, who would fall
in love with a freak show like you?
(CHUCKLING) Oh, wait, let me guess,
I bet she's got a certificate, too, huh?
- ED: Mmm-hmm.
- (LAUGHING)
- (ELECTRICITY ZAPS)
- (GROANING)
(MUFFLED) What do you want?
Tell me what you want?
Tell me what you want.
I wanna break Butch's
heart before I end his life.
You know, kind of an
eye-for-an-eye thing.
But in this case,
I'll take a hand.
(DOOR OPENS)
(INHALES DEEPLY)
Is that vinegar?
Vinegar and baking soda.
Takes tarnish off anything.
Selina, that key is
hundreds of years old!
I'm not an idiot, you know?
Maybe there's something
on the key that you can't see,
because 100 years of
crap is covering it up?
Why did you tell Ivy
we weren't a couple?
- Why did you tell her we were?
- Is that a trick question?
Why can't we just be us?
Can you take that key out
now? It's making me nervous.
(SOFT CHUCKLE)
SELINA: Mmm.
There's an engraving on it.
Like a bird, or something.
Not just a bird. An owl.
- Uh... And?
- BRUCE: Alfred!
If you're right, merely possessing
this key could be seen as breaking
your agreement with the people that
the woman in the owl mask represents.
Which is why we
need to contact them.
They have to understand Ivy
didn't know what she was stealing.
Wait. Where is she anyhow?
Oh, bloody hell. She's gone.
How did she disable the alarm?
Don't worry about
that now, all right?
What's the big deal? She'll
be back when she's hungry.
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
Wayne Manor.
VOLK: You have the
necklace, we have your friend.
We make exchange, no?
Where and when?
We're supposed to
go down the manhole?
That's what they said. All right,
give me the key. I'll sort it out.
No. I need to speak
with them personally.
Make sure they understand
this was a mistake.
Very well, Master Bruce.
There's no way of
asking you to stay here
that doesn't end with
you yelling at me, is there?
No.
BRUCE: Over there.
- SELINA: Ivy?
- It's about time.
My name is Bruce Wayne. I
need to speak with Kathryn.
She needs to understand
I've honored our deal.
Hand over the necklace, and you
get your friend back. That's the deal.
You mean the key, don't you?
You're not getting it back until I
talk to the people you work for.
Maybe we just
kill you and take it?
You think we're stupid
enough to bring it with us?
You really want it
back, I'd listen to him.
Put the tools
down. All right? Eh?
I need reassurances my friends
are no longer in any danger.
I need to speak to the
woman in the mask.
Any assurances that
woman gives you are lies.
How do you know?
Because the people you are
talking about have no honor.
And they will betray
you, as they betrayed us.
Wait. You don't work for them?
No. We work to destroy them.
Who are they?
They call themselves
"The Court of Owls."
(SIRENS WAILING)
- They're after Mario?
- Yes.
- Where is he?
- GCPD. He's safe. For now.
But I can't help him if you
don't tell me what's going on.
You think I'm holding
something back?
Military grade
explosion? The clean-up?
A sword-wielding
assassin in broad daylight.
This doesn't feel
like a mob grudge.
What else is there?
Could Mario be
mixed up in something?
- Is that what you came to ask me?
- I'm working the evidence I have.
I understand why
you'd want to believe
the man who's marrying Lee
must be mixed up in something.
My son is the most decent
person I've ever known.
He's not like us.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
That just tells me there's
something you don't know.
BULLOCK: Jim, Mario's gone.
You were supposed
to keep him there.
I know, I tried,
but he said he didn't trust you
or the GCPD to take care of this.
So, he was going to.
Whatever the hell that means.
What is it?
Mario just walked
out of the GCPD.
Think he's gonna try
to finish this himself.
How?
I have a pretty good idea.
- Can I help you?
- BARBARA: I hope so.
I had something that was
supposed to be delivered to me?
Could you check your records?
Sure. Let me check the safe.
Uh, what was the last name?
"Nygma."
Oh. That item was
already delivered.
Great.
Well, I guess as long
as I'm already here
I should pick up something
for the weekend. Right?
(SOFTLY) Mmm.
Well, this looks fun.
Could I ask a favor of you?
- Uh, Todd.
- Todd.
Could you show
me how this works?
(SIGHS)
We're not really supposed
to... (CLEARS THROAT)
I won't tell if you don't.
It's pretty basic, really.
Um, you just put your
arms through here,
and then your head through
here, and then you bring it up.
And then... Oh!
Do you like role play, Todd?
Good.
I will play the beautiful,
coquettish bank robber
who needs to get into that safe,
and you get to play the
lucky, young shopkeeper
who gives her the
combination, okay?
My friend was taken
by this man, Nygma.
I need to know where she is.
If I find her, I could come back
here and personally thank you.
(WHIMPERING)
Give Mommy the combination.
(STAMMERING) Nine, 25, 72.
Good.
(SIGHS)
Nygma, you sick bastard.
(STAMMERING) Hey?
You can't just leave me here!
Hello?
(GASPS) Oh, goodie!
You're finally awake.
The show continues.
(MIMICKING DRUMROLL)
Ta-da!
I designed it myself.
You wanna see
how it works? Okay!
I love a captive audience.
So, we'll set the timer
for, say, 55 seconds.
Now, when the timer hits zero,
the spring-loaded blade is released.
- (TIMER TICKING)
- Simple. Now, for the fun part.
You can stop the blade from being
released, if you click this little button.
But if you do,
it will send a fatal jolt of
electricity to zap Butch.
It's a simple test, really.
Stop the blade from
falling and kill Butch, or...
(TIMER DINGS)
Mmm!
The choice...
(GRUNTS)
my dear, is yours.
Will we hear the
zap of heartbreak,
or the sound of
one-hand clapping.
(LAUGHING)
(METAL CHAINS CLINKING)
My name is Volk.
(CUFFS CLICK)
My brother, Jacob,
and that's Dmitry.
What's with the stupid mask?
I like you. You remind
me of my sister in Kiev.
Dmitry is an initiate.
The mask ensures his
silence until he proves himself
and becomes a full member.
Of what? Who are you?
We are called "the Whisper Gang."
Gotham's most notorious smugglers.
We used to number in the hundreds
until the Court saw our growing strength
and they offered
us a partnership,
only to betray us.
Many escaped back to Ukraine,
but a few of us stayed back,
hoping to find a way
to enact revenge.
- And we did.
- The key?
But what does it open?
A safe.
It is in one of the
Court's buildings, here.
Inside, there is a device that
we believe can destroy them.
What? Like some kind of weapon?
Oh, honestly, we don't know.
We captured a member.
But even he didn't know
what's inside the safe.
Only that the Court fears it falling
into the hands of their enemies.
Wait, wouldn't they
know you stole it?
They're probably waiting
for you to show up there.
No. Because, originally,
the safe had two keys.
The Court still has one of them.
And the second one was thought lost.
Until we found it.
You mean, we did?
The Court of Owls
killed my parents.
I stood down because I thought
there was no way to defeat them.
What are you proposing?
If what you're saying is true,
and there is something in that safe,
then that's no longer the case.
(DOOR OPENS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
JIM: Mario?
You really think this is a good
idea? Using yourself as bait?
If those guys are out
there, Lee isn't safe.
They're pros. You're
gonna get killed.
What do you care?
- Why would someone wanna kill you?
- I have no idea.
Because it seems to me
an operation like this
doesn't happen for no reason.
And putting yourself
in the cross hairs
feels a lot like someone
protecting a secret.
I wanna protect Lee. That's it.
We're sitting ducks in here. We
need to get away from bystanders.
- They're here.
- What?
Get down!
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
WOMAN: No! No!
(GROANS)
(MEN GRUNTING)
(MARIO STRAINING)
(SCREAMING)
You could have killed
her! Who sent you?
Why are you coming after me?
(CHOKING) You know why.
(GRUNTS)
- (SIRENS WAILING)
- (HANDCUFFS CLICKING)
(BUTCH AND TABITHA GRUNTING)
Hey, Ed, come on. Come
on, let's talk about this, huh?
Come on, Ed. You
don't have to do this.
Come on, let's talk about
this. Come on! Listen!
I told you, I've never heard
of anyone named Isabelle.
Isabella! Why is
that so difficult?
Also, I'm not the one you
should be pleading with.
Your life is in her hand.
What difference does it make?
You're gonna kill me one
way, or the other, right?
Good point. (CHUCKLES)
New deal.
If she loves you enough to
sacrifice her hand. Twinsies.
In exchange for your life.
I swear on the memory
of my beloved Isabella,
I will set you both free.
(CLICKING)
(TIMER TICKING)
Tabby, baby, you don't wanna...
- We can get out of here. We can...
- I like you, Butch. I really do.
But to be completely honest, I'm
not exactly in a love place right now.
(LAUGHS)
Sorry, big fella.
I wish I could say that I was surprised,
but I knew that she was going to say that.
(WHISPERS) It's
why I made the offer.
Any final words? I
would keep it brief.
BUTCH: Tabby, baby,
the last few weeks have
been the best of my life.
And it's okay you don't love me.
'Cause I love you.
And for a guy like
me, that's enough.
And, you, you're
damn right I killed her.
I killed the woman you loved.
You know what she said to me
right before I put a bullet in her brain?
You know what she told me?
She said she wished she
would've been with a real man.
Hey, Butch?
Yeah?
You're sweet.
No! No!
(GASPS)
Untie me!
Please untie me! She's
gotta get to a hospital! Quick!
You said that you put
a bullet in her head.
Isabella died in a car crash.
The break lines were cut.
I don't care! I told you
I never heard of her.
You really didn't kill her?
No! Untie me! She's gotta
get to a hospital! Come on!
(GUN COCKS)
I'd put that hand on some ice.
(HORNS BLARING)
Neither of you recognize him?
No.
Has he said anything?
Not a peep.
Hey. I ran your guy's prints.
They're not in the system.
Which, considering he's a pro,
wasn't that hard to believe.
I know. Still. Now, that we
have him, we should work him.
Find out who's behind this.
You better act
quick. Call came in.
They're transferring him
to a Federal facility upstate.
What! No, no, no. We
can't let this guy leave!
What can I do? My hands were
tied. The Feds want him, they get him.
Question is why.
Maybe somebody wants
him out of this precinct.
Away from us.
I don't know anyone with
that kind of pull. Do you?
JIM: The other assassin.
You wanna tell me what
happened in the store?
There's nothing to tell. He came
after me, I did what I needed to do.
You called her?
She deserves to know what's
going on. Either you tell her, or I will.
(DOOR CLOSES)
FALCONE: I think I
know who sent you,
but I need to know for sure.
And we both know that
you're not going to tell me.
So...
So, how does it feel?
BULLOCK: I don't know.
Maybe I could be Captain?
Yell at people for
not having proof,
or at one of my detectives
for going after a pair of
assassins all by his lonesome!
- Not bad.
- Right?
Very interesting
play, by the way.
It's not every day
that you get to save
the man who's marrying
the woman you love.
Yeah. I'm really something.
It's not too late, Jim.
Lee deserves to
know how you feel.
God knows I know that
life gives us enough regret.
There's no need adding to it.
- Oh, crap.
- I know it's hard.
It's just, it's something
you have to...
Falcone!
(ASSASSIN SCREAMING)
(CONTINUES SCREAMING)
(COUGHING)
(BLOOD SPUTTERING)
(ASSASSIN SPITS)
(DOOR OPENS)
Falcone, up against the wall.
- What're you doing?
- Just having a chat.
Turns out our friend here works
for a former associate of mine.
So, now that I know who's
behind this, I can take care of it.
My way. It's over.
You think you're
gonna walk away?
You just assaulted a
suspect in police custody.
He won't be pressing charges.
I'm gonna find out what happened
today. Who's pulling the strings.
And how Mario's
involved. Trust me.
If I were you, I'd let it go.
VOLK: Gather the men.
Tell them we're joining
forces with the boy.
I will brief them
tomorrow night myself.
TALON: Volk!
Dmitry, eyes!
(CHOKES)
We know you've been
searching for the second key.
Have you found it?
(BOTH GRUNTING)
I'll ask you again.
Have you found the second key?
(GROWLING) Why don't
you ask Dmitry? Huh?
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(SCREAMS AND GROANS)
(BLOOD DRIPPING)
(SIRENS WAILING)
You think she'll be okay? Think
they can reattach the hand?
Please. She's tough
as nails. She'll be fine.
BUTCH: You know
this is war, right?
Nygma, Penguin, anyone who
stands with them, they're all dead.
This woman, Isabella. Nygma
said she was a librarian, right?
Well, who kills a librarian?
I mean, what's the motive?
I don't know.
Maybe someone had an overdue
book and things got out of hand.
Excuse me, but
you just can't walk...
Come on! Come on! I got it.
NURSE: We got a
hand here, people! Hand!
You cut someone's break lines, you
know where they're going and when.
You know...
You know them.
(LAUGHS)
I know who did it.
I know who killed the librarian.
Who?
The same person
who's in love with Nygma,
and doesn't wanna
share him. (GIGGLING)
Okay. One woman in love
with that psychotic bean pole
defies explanation, but two?
Who said anything about a woman?
(BARBARA CHUCKLES)
I am tired of sitting
at the kids table.
If I'm right, we can have
way more than vengeance.
We can have it all.
We don't need to go to war.
All we need to do is start one.
(BARBARA GIGGLING)
There must've been some mistake.
We don't make mistakes.
I've always done whatever
the Court has asked of me.
Even against my own interest.
I got you Indian Hill when
Maroni refused to sell.
No one is questioning
your loyalty.
If this isn't about me, then
why are you trying to kill my son?
There are things
you're not privy to.
That's not an answer!
It will have to do.
We both know the level
of disruption I can cause.
You think we're scared of you?
The car bomb was designed
to look like a mob hit.
You didn't want me to
find out it was you. I have.
I don't care about your reasons.
If my son is harmed in any way,
I will come after you
with everything I have.
You won't win.
If my son is dead,
winning won't be the point.
Gotham will burn.
This city is on
the brink of chaos.
Only we can save it.
We will expect your
assistance when called on.
Until then, your son is safe.
At least from us.
What aren't you telling me?
A great many things.
Enjoy your dinner.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
(KNOCKING CONTINUES)
Hey.
Is everything okay?
I was on my way to
the rehearsal dinner,
then I heard myself telling
the cab driver your address.
Mario told me
everything about today.
How you risked your
own life to make sure...
I didn't do it for him.
I know.
He's a good man.
Uh-huh.
Tell me.
What?
What you have to tell me.
I missed my chance to
give you the life you deserve.
To make you happy.
But I do want that for you.
More than anything.
Why does it feel like we
keep saying goodbye?
Maybe it's all we have left.
Or we just haven't
done it properly yet.
Goodbye, James Gordon.
(DOOR OPENS)
MAN: Yo, Peeping Tom! You lost?
Lucky for you,
we sell directions!
Price, everything you've got.
MARIO: She loves him.
She loves him. She loves him.
You deaf?
MARIO: She loves him.
- I said...
- MARIO: She loves him.
Hey, man! What...
(MAN GROANING)
- (CHOKING)
- She loves me! And I won't let her go!
She loves me!
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
English -SDH